(Leonard:)We're going to Long Beach?
(Sheldon:)Of course not, there's no cousin Leo,
there's no intervention.
(Sheldon:)- Focus, Leonard.
- Oh, come on.
(Sheldon:)We just leave the house on Friday night
and return in the wee hours...
(Sheldon:)...emotionally wrung out from the work
of convincing Leo to go back into rehab.
(Leonard:)So he goes back into rehab?
(Sheldon:)Yes, but he can relapse if Penny
ever invites us to hear her sing again.
(Leonard:)You still told her I lied.
Yeah, for a noble purpose.
(Sheldon:)To spare me the social embarrassment
of having a drug-addled first cousin.
(Sheldon:)- Which I'm assuming is embarrassing, yes?
- I don't know.
- How am I supposed to remember all this?
- That's the best part, you don't have to.
(Sheldon:)I told Penny that you would be embarrassed
if you knew she found out you had lied...
(Sheldon:)...so she's agreed to operate
as if the original lie is still in force.
(Leonard:)So she's expecting me to lie
about going to a symposium in Pasadena...
(Leonard:)...when in actuality, we're pretending to go
to a drug intervention in Long Beach.